# Kirill Elizarov

.NET Developer

Prague, Czech Republic

**\( +420779970567** 

@ kiril.elizarov@gmail.com

#### Links

in Kirill Elizarov

kulebyaka

#### Skills

# **Technical Skills**

a.k.a. buzzwords

C#, REST API, NUnit, Entity Framework, Angular, React, ASP webforms, Azure, PostgreSQL, Oracle, MS SQL, TFS, git, TeamCity, Rider, VS, ReSharper, Postman, .Net Core, Vue.js, Episerver, Docker, k8s, Python, LLM, Octopus

# Languages

#### Czech

Advanced professional proficiency

#### English

Upper intermediate

#### Russian

Native proficiency

#### Certifications

#### Systems Design Fundamentals AlgoExpert 2020

Comprehensive systems design

fundamentals certification

# Angular 2 Basic

angular.cz

February 2019

Comprehensive training in Angular 2 framework and development practices

#### React JS and Redux Bootcamp udemy 2019

Comprehensive React and Redux

development course

#### CCNA Routing and Switching Cisco Systems January 2010

Cisco Certified Network Associate certification in routing and switching

# Interests

#### Hobbies

Game development (Unity), IoT, squash, hiking, tennis

## Summary

Software engineer with 10 years of experience in developing complex applications in the banking, e-commerce and B2B sectors. Experienced in leading teams and developing new products from scratch within strict deadlines and providing long-term support for systems with large backlogs. Strong focus on architectural solutions and technical leadership.

# Experience

#### First Line Software

Senior .NET Developer & Tech Lead https://firstlinesoftware.com/

Kin+Carta various projects, development:

- Successfully participated in development and delivey over 10 enterprise-level projects, including implementations for major clients such as Pizza Hut and the UK National Football League
- Enhanced Episerver CMS platform with advanced features including AIpowered content recommendations and search result optimization
- Triptych, technical leadership (December 2021 November 2022):
  - Led the development of the Triptych sales content management platform, with particular focus on scalability, security, and seamless CRM integration
  - Architected and implemented core platform features, including sophisticated content customization tools and advanced analytics capabilities
  - Orchestrated client communications and feature rollouts, ensuring alignment with business objectives and stakeholder requirements
  - Spearheaded the migration to microservices architecture while modernizing infrastructure to implement robust CI/CD practices and enhance system resilience

#### SKB Kontur

Back End Developer, Team Leader

March 2020 - December 2020

April 2021 - Present

Prague, CZ

Prague

- Led the development of a service for small businesses: an Electronic Sales Registration (ESR) system
- Key responsibilities:
  - System design and task delegation
  - API development
  - Maintenance of technical documentation
  - CI/CD configuring

#### Cleverlance

.NET Developer

https://www.cleverlance.com

August 2017 - March 2021 Prague, CZ

- Development of an application for approving corporate credit products, covering the entire approval workflow: tasks, design and approval of financing, risk analysis, contractual documentation, and loan drawdown
- Key responsibilities:
  - Design and implementation of architectural solutions based on functional specifications
  - Incident management

# Spring Systems, s.r.o.

ASP.NET Developer

October 2015 - July 2017 Prague

- Development and support of a benefit system
- Key contributions:
  - Development of a tree-like task management system with change history tracking
  - Creating demo versions and prototyping new features

#### Education

#### **Ural State University** Applied Mathematics

September 2007 - August 2012

Bachelor's degree in Applied Mathematics with focus on software development and mathematical modeling